Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
Mus. Arc. 81
Haupt, Irene
1 USB flash drive (250 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 250 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo 2018 at the University at Buffalo, including guest composers John Harbison, Roger Reynolds, Hilda Paredes, Hans Thomalla, and Louis Karchin.
All files in the collection were renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Original filenames stated in the container list are transcribed as stated on the flash drive as received. Renamed files are stored in the Institutional Repository.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2018.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2018 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2018 contains 250 digital images of participants in the festival for 2018. The list of musicians includes faculty composers David Felder, John Harbison, Roger Reynolds, Hilda Paredes, Hans Thomalla, and Louis Karchin. Performers include Brad Lubman, Irvine Arditti, Moon Young Ha, Matthew Chamberlain, Tiffany DuMouchelle, and JoAnn Falletta. Ensembles include the Mivos Ensemble, Ensemble Mise-En, Ensemble Signal, Slee Sinfonietta, and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra.
Arrangement
One series chiefly arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Composer Louis Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9480.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_001.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9480BW.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_002.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9481.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_003.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9483.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_004.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaching Matthew Chamberlain, conductor as Slee Sinfonietta member Hanna Hurwitz, violin looks on in rehearsal of Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9486.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_005.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaching Matthew Chamberlain, conductor as Slee Sinfonietta member Hanna Hurwitz, violin looks on in rehearsal of Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9487.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_006.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaching Matthew Chamberlain, conductor in rehearsal of Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9492.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_007.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaching Matthew Chamberlain, conductor as Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn and Will Knuth, violin look on in rehearsal of Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9493.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_008.tif)
- June in Buffalo managing director Robert Phillips speaks to Matthew Chamberlain, conductor as Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, and Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin look on in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9495.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_009.tif)
- June in Buffalo managing director Robert Phillips speaks to Matthew Chamberlain, conductor as Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, and Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin look on in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9496.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_010.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter with Slee Sinfonietta members Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, and Will Knuth and Hanna Hurwitz, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9500.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_011.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter with Slee Sinfonietta members Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, and Will Knuth and Hanna Hurwitz, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9501.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_012.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, and Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Thomas Meglioranza, baritone on his piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9510.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_013.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, and Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Thomas Meglioranza, baritone on his piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9511.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_014.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth and Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, and Daniel Brottman, horn rehearse Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9514.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_015.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, and Michal Matsuno, flute on his piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9522.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_016.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Thomas Meglioranza, baritone talk and laugh as Slee Sinfonietta members Jonathan Golove, violoncello and Will Knuth, violin look on in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9523.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_017.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Matsuno, flute and Daniel Brottman, horn look at a piece of music and smile in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9528.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_018.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Matsuno, flute and Daniel Brottman, horn look at a piece of music in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9531.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_019.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin talks with Slee Sinfonietta member Jean Kopperud, clarinet on a break from rehearsing Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9532.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_020.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn and Michael Matsuno, flute look at a piece of music in rehearsal of Louis Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9534.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_021.tif)
- June in Buffalo managing director Robert Phillips and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Will Knuth, violin on break from rehearsing Louis Karchin's pieces as Slee Sinfonietta member Jean Kopperud, clarinet speaks with Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9538.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_022.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin prepares Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano and Will Knuth, violin to rehearse Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9539.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_023.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin prepares Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, and Will Knuth, violin to rehearse Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9540.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_024.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin prepares Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, and Will Knuth, violin to rehearse Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9542.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_025.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin prepares Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Daniel Brottman, horn, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, and Will Knuth, violin to rehearse Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9543.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_026.tif)
- Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano rehearses composer Louis Karchin's Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9545.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_027.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses composer Louis Karchin's Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney with Slee Sinfonietta members Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Christopher Guzman, piano, Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9549.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_028.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano as Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and other Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno flute on Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9550composer Louis Karchin.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_029.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain rehearses composer Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter with Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Matsuno, flute, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Daniel Brottman, horn, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Christopher Guzman, piano at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Untitled-1 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_030.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain rehearses composer Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter with Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Matsuno, flute, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, Daniel Brottman, horn, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Christopher Guzman, piano at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name UntiSlee.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_031.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin poses with student composers William David Cooper, Weijun Chen, Clay Mettens, Reilly Spitzfaden, Alon Nechushtan, and Kai-Young Chan at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9555.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_032.tif)
- Student composers Fernando Munizaga, Seong Ae Kim, Ioannis Mitsialis, Yi-Hsien Chen, Kyle Puebla Dubin, Reilly Spitzfaden, and Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9557.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_033.tif)
- Student composers Fernando Munizaga, Seong Ae Kim, xxx, Kyle Puebla Dubin, Ioannis Mitsialis, Yi-Hsien Chen, Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen, Reilly Spitzfaden, Dylan Findley, Kurt Nelson, Kezia Yap, and Yotam Haber at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9559.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_034.tif)
- Composer David Felder poses with student composers Fernando Munizaga, Seong Ae Kim, xxx, Kyle Puebla Dubin, Ioannis Mitsialis, Yi-Hsien Chen, Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen, Reilly Spitzfaden, Dylan Findley, Kurt Nelson, Kezia Yap, and Yotam Haber at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9561.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_035.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin and David Felder, composer chat outside June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_036.tif)
- Video plays during the student composer introduction at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00476.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_037.tif)
- Video plays during the student composer introduction at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00477.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_038.tif)
- Composer David Felder addresses student composers at an introduction to June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00478.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_039.tif)
- Thomas Meglioranza rehearses Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9577.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_040.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Hanna Hurwitz, Will Knuth, Jonathan Golove, Thomas Meglioranza, voice, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9579.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_041.tif)
- Thomas Meglioranza rehearses Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9583.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_042.tif)
- Thomas Meglioranza rehearses Louis Karchin's Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9586.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_043.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin coaches Thomas Meglioranza, baritone on Karchin's piece Gods of Winter as Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin, Daniel Brottman, horn, and Michael Matsuno, flute look on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name baritone.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_044.tif)
- Thomas Meglioranza, baritone and Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano pose at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9591.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_045.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin poses with Thomas Meglioranza, baritone and Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9597.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_046.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin and Alyssa Roggow, viola rehearsing composer John Harbison's piece Mirabai Songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9599.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_047.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses John Harbison's piece Mirabai Songs with Slee Sinfonietta members Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Michael Matsuno, flute, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Alyssa Roggow, viola, and Kristen Theriault, harp at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9606.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_048.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses John Harbison's piece Mirabai Songs with Slee Sinfonietta members Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Michael Matsuno, flute, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Kristen Theriault, harp, and Stephen Solook, percussion at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9614.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_049.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Kristen Theriault, harp, and Stephen Solook, percussion rehearse John Harbison's piece Mirabai Songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9616.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_050.tif)